[
    {
        "question" :"What is the full form of Ajax?",
        "a":"Asynchronous JavaScript And XML",
        "b":"Asynchronous jQuery And XML",
        "c":"Asynchronous JavaScript And XHTML",
        "d":"Asynchronous jQuery And XHTML",
        "answer":"Asynchronous JavaScript And XML"
    
    },
    {
        "question" :"In AJAX you can ",
        "a":"Update a web page without reloading the page",
        "b":"Receive data from a server - after the page has loaded",
        "c":"Send data to a server - in the background",
        "d":"All of the above",
        "answer":"All of the above"
    
    },
    {
        "question" :"What is the name of the object used for AJAX request?",
        "a":"HttpRequest",
        "b":"xmlRequest",
        "c":"XMLHTTPRequest",
        "d":"Request",
        "answer":"XMLHTTPRequest"
    
    },
    {
        "question" :"Ajax is aâ€¦",
        "a":"Programing Language",
        "b":"Technology",
        "c":"OOPs concepts",
        "d":"Options B and C",
        "answer":"Technology"
    
    },
    {
        "question" :"Implementing AJAX in our websites we can make our web pages ________ ?",
        "a":"More Dynamic",
        "b":"More interactive and faster ",
        "c":"More Responsive",
        "d":"Easy to connect web page with server",
        "answer":"More interactive and faster "
    
    },
    {
        "question" :"AJAX allows web page to dynamically",
        "a":"Change content",
        "b":"Reload at times",
        "c":"Control other pages",
        "d":"Connect to other addresses",
        "answer":"Change content"
    
    },
     {
        "question" :"_____ Of the following technologies, which one provides the ability to dynamically interact with Web page layout?",
        "a":"XML",
        "b":"HTML",
        "c":"JavaScript",
        "d":"Document Object Model",
        "answer":"Document Object Model"
    
    },
    {
        "question" :"What does the XMLHttpRequest object accomplish in Ajax?",
        "a":"It provides the ability to asynchronously exchange data between Web browser and a Web server",
        "b":"It's the programming language used to develop Ajax applications",
        "c":"It provides the ability to markup and style the display of web-page text",
        "d":"It provides a means of exchanging structured data between the Web server and client",
        "answer":"It provides the ability to asynchronously exchange data between Web browser and a Web server"
    
    },
    {
        "question" :" What two main structures compose JSON?",
        "a":"Key and value",
        "b":"Class and Object",
        "c":"Arrays and Objects",
        "d":"None of the above",
        "answer":"Key and value"
    
    },
    {
        "question" :"Which is the correct format of writing a json name/value pair?",
        "a":"name : value'",
        "b":"name : val'",
        "c":"name = value'",
        "d":"All of the Above",
        "answer":"name : value'"
    
    }
]
